(Howard:)Okay, Raj...
(Howard:)...hand me the number six
Torx screwdriver.
(Sheldon:)Stop.
(Sheldon:)We can't do this. It's not right.
Sheldon, you have got two choices.
(Raj:)Put a bigger hard drive in the TiVo
or delete stuff before we go out of town.
(Sheldon:)But once you open the box,
you've voided the warranty.
(Sheldon:)The warranty is a sacred covenant
we've entered into with the manufacturer.
(Sheldon:)He offers to stand by his equipment.
(Sheldon:)We in return agree not to violate
the integrity of the internal hardware.
(Sheldon:)This little orange sticker is all that stands
between us and anarchy.
(Howard:)Okay,
then we won't touch the hard drive.
(Leonard:)We'll just erase the first season
of Battlestar.
(Sheldon(ripping off sticker):)There. We're outlaws.
- Here you go, Leonard. Is this big enough?
- It's perfect.
(Howard:)For taking daffodils to your unicorn.
(Leonard:)It's just for my notebooks.
Thanks, Penny.